Register of the S. I. Hayakawa papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Washington Office, Administrative/Legislative Files (Boxes 1-265)
  - Press tapes - audio
    - speech, Mt. Olive Baptist Church, 9/11/77
    - press conference, re: tax cuts, 9/12/77
    - interview with Radio News West, re: Reclamation Act Proposals, 9/20/77
    - testimony, Subcommittee on Parks and Recreation, re: Endangered Wilderness Act, 9/20/77
    - speech, Cheltenham Five-Star Forum, Wyncote, PA, 9/27/77
    - speech, Commonwealth Club, re: SALT II, 11/4/77
    - speech, California Federation of Republican Women, Fresno; 11/4/77, San Francisco Commonwealth Club, re: SALT, 10/12/77
    - speech, JACL Annual District Conference, Fresno, 11/21/77
    - speech, Constituency Council, Pasadena, 11/19/77
    - phone interview, Tahoe News, John Gonzales, 11/21/77
    - interview, WGBH (Public TV), 12/5/77
    - press conference, re: California Advisory Committees, 12/5/77
    - interview with Japanese reporters, Yomiuri Shimbun, 12/9/77
    - press conference, re: B-1 bomber, 12/14/77
    - press conference, re: B-1 bomber, 12/15/77
    - press conference, San Francisco, before trip to Japan, 1/4/78
    - press conference, Andrews Air Force Base on return from USSR, 1/11/78
    - press conference, re: trip to USSR, 1/12/78
    - press conference, re: trip to Japan, 1/17/78
    - interview with Orvin L. Wilhite, Chief, Division of Agriculture, Bureau of Census, 1/18/78
    - press conference, Washington, D.C., 1/23/78
    - press conference, Forum on Regulation, 1/24/78
    - Actuality, Redwoods, 1/25/78
    - interview, Chicago Tribune, quality of speeches in Senate, 1/25/78
    - testimony, re: Panama Canal, 1/31/78
    - speech, re: Panama Canal, 1/31/78
    - floor statement, B-1 bomber, 2/1/78
    - speech, response to House of Repesentatives, passage of Redwoods Bill, 2/9/78
    - interview, Jim Gannon of Wall Street Journal, 2/10/78
    - speech, United Fruit Growers Association, Los Angeles, 2/15/78
    - Forum, Hayakawa and Moynihan at American Association of School Administrators meeting, 2/20/78 (Box 224)
    - speech, Labor Policy Association meeting, 2/25/78
    - speech, Union League club of New York City, 3/78
    - interview, Cinesell Nipponese Network, re: US/Japanese economy, 3/1/78
    - testimony, Senate Committee on Banking, Housing, and Urban Affairs, 3/1/78
    - panel discussion, Competency Testing, National Institute of Education, 3/2/78
    - interview with Shirley Elder, US Magazine, 3/2/78
    - speech, International Management and Development Institute, Japanese/US trade, 3/7/78
    - speech, international economics, 3/7/78
    - interview by telephone, Airway Magazine with Milt Rockmore, 3/7/78
    - Actuality, re: increasing teenage unemployment, 3/8/78
    - testimony, Subcommittee on Constitution of the Senate, Judiciary Committee, 3/14/78
    - interview, re: limitation on elective terms of office, 3/15/78
    - floor speech, re: Panama Canal, 3/16/78
    - speech, National Association of Realtors, 3/12/78
    - press conference, 3/20/78
    - testimony of Ray Marshall, Human Resources Committee, 3/22/78
    - interview with Valerie Strauss, Jack Anderson's Radio Show, 3/23/78
    - speech, California High School students, 3/29/78
    - speech and press conference, Jewish Federation, 3/30/78
    - Actuality, re: Panama Canal, 4/78
    - interview with Sue Mathis, re: Panama Canal vote, 4/78
    - interview, CWA of California; speech, South Pasadena Junior High School, 4/4/78
    - testimony, Public Works Appropriation Subcommittee, 4/5/78
    - statement, Budget Committee Mark-up (2 tapes), 4/7/78
    - speech, California Bankers Association Delegation, 4/11/78
    - statement, re: land reclamation and subsidies, Energy and Natural Resources Committee, 4/12/78
    - speech to students, 4/13/78
    - press conference, Panama Canal, 4/14/78
    - Actuality, re: foreign relations decisions made after Panama Canal vote, 4/18/78
    - Actuality, Jarvis-Gann, 4/18/78
    - floor statement, re: labor reform, 4/18/78
    - press conference with California Press, 4/24/78
    - speech, re: two party system, San Jose Junior High, 4/25/78
    - conference, "Asia - A Market for US Business", 4/25/78
    - interview with Hal Cessna, Cox Broadcasting, 4/26/78
    - speech, Winters, California Retired Persons, 4/26/78
    - speech, NBRG Conference, 6/78
    - testimony, re: mineral king, 4/28/78
    - interview with Marty Salditch, 5/78
    - testimony, re: illegal aliens, Subcommittee on the Constitution, 5/3/78
    - floor filibuster, re: labor reform, 5/17/78
    - press conference, Jarvis-Gann Initiative, 5/18/78
    - interview with Mike Certhbert, WGMS, re: free enterprise, 5/18/78
    - speech, Republican Women Forum Luncheon, 5/18/78
    - interview with Ken Breck, Congregate Housing for the Elderly, 5/18/78
    - press conference, re: trip to Africa, 5/24/78
    - press conference; press conference, re: trip to Africa, 5/24/78
    - press conference, re: trip to Africa, 6/8/78
    - testimony, re: teenage pregnancy, Committee on Human Resources, 6/14/78
    - press conference, Howard Jarvis, 6/19/78
    - speech, Foreign Policy Association of South Africa, Mayflower Hotel, 6/21/78
    - interview with Bob Duke, Scripps-Howard, 6/23/78
    - press conference, re: Bakke Decision, 6/28/78
    - interview with Rita Kemply, Dossier magazine, 6/28/78
    - speech, Soroptimist International Biennial Convention, 7/3/78
    - speech, Voice of Agriculture, 7/6/78
    - meeting with ERA Lobbyists, 7/10/78
    - interview with Ruth Thompson, re: South Africa, 7/12/78
    - Actuality, re: Andrew Young, 7/14/78
    - interview with Mort Young, Hearst newspapers, 7/13/78
    - press conference with Bishop Muzorewa of Rhodesia, 7/18/78 (Box 225)
    - press conference, general discussion (2 tapes), 7/20/78
    - interview, re: Japanese internment, Cox Broadcasting, 7/25/78
    - interview, William Raspberry of MTGW, 7/27/78
    - interview, Barbara Walters, ABC, 8/2/78
    - interview with Leroy Aarons, People magazine, 8/2/78
    - interview with Henry Rosen, re: accuracy in media, 8/4/78
    - speech, Los Angeles Chinatown Lions, 8/5/78
    - press conference with Senator Packwood, re: race and tuition tax credit, 8/8/78
    - speech, interns from UCLA, Berkeley, and Stanford, 8/8/78
    - floor statement, re: D.C. voting rights, 8/18/78
    - floor statement, re: D.C. voting rights, 8/22/78
    - press conference (2 tapes), 8/24/78
    - interview, Cox Broadcasting, 8/25/78
    - Actuality, re: D.C. voting rights, 8/25/78
    - speech, California Association of Realtors, Los Angeles, 8/26/78
    - interview, re: Japanese trade talks, Japan TV, 9/8/78
    - speech, Republican Finance Committee Fundraiser of Missouri (2 tapes), 9/9/78
    - interview along with Senator Chaffee, re: Tax Cut Blitz, WGIL, 9/20/78
    - interview with Ed Nichold, San Diego Union, 9/21/78
    - press conference, State Department briefing, 9/22/78
    - press conference, re: Transafrica, 9/22/78
    - speech, Republican Eagles, Palm Springs, 9/23/78
    - press conference, Congressional Black Caucus, 9/26/78
    - editorial, WCBS, re: D.C. voting rights, 9/27/78
    - press conference, California, 9/28/78
    - press conference, California, 10/78
    - interview with Abe Anel Shimbuh, 10/2/78
    - press conference with 5 Senators, re: Rhodesia (2 copies), 10/2/78
    - press conference, re: Rhodesia, 10/5/78
    - interview, Canadian TV, 10/5/78
    - speech, California Community College administration, 10/5/78
    - joint press conference, re: wage/price controls, 10/5/78
    - interview with Jim Martin, 10/8/78
    - press conference, Ian Smith and Reverend Sithole, 10/9/78
    - interview with SDF (German TV), 10/9/78
    - interview, Rhodesian TV, 10/10/78
    - press conference, California, 10/12/78
    - interview, US News and World Report, 10/12/78
    - Muzorewa/Chiran address Senate staff, 10/17/78
    - speech, Automotive Parts Rebuilders Association; speech, African Institute of CPAs, 10/23/78
    - speech, National Foundry Association, 11/3/78
    - Japanese Chamber of Commerce, 11/9/78
    - speech, San Bernardino Chamber of Commerce, 11/10/78
    - speech, Riverside, California, 11/10/78
    - speech, National Association of Independent Insurers, 11/14/78
    - speech, Nova High School, Redding, California, 11/29/78
    - speech, Riverside Chamber of Commerce, 11/29/78
    - speech, Shasta College, Redding, California, 11/29/78
    - speech, Yolo County Constitutional Council, 11/30/78
    - questions and answers, Sacramento State, 12/1/78
    - questions and answers, San Francisco State, 12/1/78
    - speech, Kennedy High School, Sacramento, 12/1/78
    - speech, Hiram Johnson High School Sacramento, 12/1/78
    - questions and answers, San Francisco State; speech, El Dorado County Constituency Council, 12/2/78
    - Larry Pascal (SIH District Representative), Youth Program Seminar, 12/2/78
  - Videotapes (Box 226)
    - Tom Pettit, NBC News, Intro to new Senators; "Play It Again, Sam"' SF student demonstration; Senate Committee; Office Shot; Reception Shot, 3/31/77
    - speech at Turlock, CA; Political process and linguistics; Japan trip, refers to 1976 elections, 2/16/78
    - press conference, Washington, letter to Carter (impossible to suport foreign policy on bipartisan basis: Ian Smith, neutron bomb, Ethiopia, SALT, Panama Canal), 4/14/78
    - interview with Hal Cessna, Cox Broadcasting, "Our Man in the Capital," Washington, D.C. (Panama Canal, taxes, previews Africa trip), 4/26/78
    - briefing for colleagues, Africa trip of May 24 - June 7, 1978, Washington, D.C., 6/16/78
    - interview, Barbara Walters for ABC News, Washington, D.C., 8/29/78
    - press conference, Senator Hayakawa with Ian Smith, Washington, D.C., 10/9/78
    - Post African trip, message to Fresno Constituency on African trip, May 24/June 7, 1978
  - Press tapes - audio (Box 227)
    - speech, California Western Law School, Press conference California, 12/5/78
    - speech, University of San Diego, 12/6/78
    - speech, San Diego High School; speech Chula Vista Chamber of Commerce; interview, San Diego Union editorial board; speech, Beverly Hills High School, 12/6/78
    - speech, Azusa Pacific College, re: two party system; speech, Beverly Hills High School, 12/7/78
    - interview, Mike O'Connor of KTVU-TV, Oakland; press interview, San Francisco, 12/12/78
    - speech, re: trade deficit and recognition of China, 12/13/78
    - press conference, Fresno; speech, Las Lomas High School, 12/14/78
    - questions and answers, California State, Bakersfield, Youth Advisory Council; speech re: D. C. voting rights, Bakersfield Chamber of Commerce, 12/15/78
    - press conference, re: China, 12/16/78
    - speech, Orange County World Affairs Council, 12/18/78
    - speech, Novato Chamber of Commerce, re: China; interview with Mike O'Connor, re: Japanese reparations, 12/19/78
    - interview, KTVU-TV, re: recognition of China, 12/20/78
    - - no date, 1979
      - Statement, Rhodesian Resolution
      - Interview, re: gas shortage, SALT, Rhodesia
      - Meeting with Constituents, re: Westlands
      - Press Conference, re: Social Security and Rhodesia
      - Speech, re: Reclamation Act, illegal aliens
      - Hearings, Foreign Relations Committee, re: Rhodesian elections
      - Interview, re: gas shortage, Rhodesia
    - interview, CBS, re: Japanese reparations, 1/3/79
    - press conference, 1/12/79
    - interview with Grace Marie Arnett, Copley News, 1/19/79
    - interview, KGO Radio Call In Show, 1/22/79
    - interview with Joe Templetom, ABC News, 1/26/79
    - speech, Traverse City Chamber of Commerce, 1/26,79
    - press release, re: Patty Hearst, 1/29/79
    - interview with Hal Cessna, Cox Broadcasting, re: Foreign Relations Committee lunch with China's Vice Premier Teng Xhiaoping, 1/30/79
    - interview, re: Teng Xhiaoping, 2/79
    - press conference, California, 2/1/79
    - interview with Ron Duhl, San Rafael Independent Journal, 2/6/79
    - press conference, 2/8/79
    - press conference, re: land reclamation, 2/8/79
    - actuality, Family Farm Liberation Act of 1979, 2/8/79
    - meeting with 4 California farmers on Parity (Tractor Group); interview wth David Hoffman, San Jose Mercury, 2/9/79
    - interview, KNBC, 2/13/79
    - speech, South Bay Commonwealth Club, press conference after speech, 2/15/79
    - speech, Republican State Central Committee, Sacramento, 2/17/79
    - interview with Richard Deystle, Voice of America, re: Africa, 2/23/79
    - press conference with George McGovern, re: Rhodesia, 2/28/79
    - Foreign Relations Committee, Rhodesia Resolution, 3/5/79
    - interview with Peter Wilshire, London Sunday Times, re: Rhodesia Resolution, 3/9/79
    - interview with David Frost, re: Rhodesia; speech, Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy students, Dirksen Office Building, 3/13/79
    - interview, National Newspapers Association, 3/15/79
    - speech, re: health, Sohio, 3/17/79
    - interview, Voice of Ameirca re: Africa, 3/20/79
    - press conference, California Radio and TV, 3/21/79
    - town meeting, SIH, McGovern, Andrew Young, Kennedy Center; testimony, Energy and Natural Resources Committee, 3/22/79
    - Press conference, California Press in SIH office, 3/28/79
    - interview with Russell Baris, Harvard Review, 3/29/79
    - floor statement, re: Rhodesian Resolution, 4/79
    - radio call in, J. Eason Show, KGO, 4/17/79
    - press conference, 4/20/79
    - Side 1: Interview with Jerry Rankin, Santa Barbara Press; Side 2: Speech, Channel City Club, re: gasoline, actuality, re: gasoline; interview with Ellen Home, 5/79
    - Keynote speech, Central Washington University, 5/6/79
    - speech, U.S. Chamber of Commerce luncheon, 5/7/79
    - press conference, JACL, 5/9/79
    - interview with Jimi Ogunlafa, Africa Report, 5/15/79
    - speech, Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, re: Rhodesia; actuality, re: gasoline, 5/17/79
    - speech, San Diego, World Affairs Council interview with Jerry Rankin, Santa Barbara Press, re: Illegal Alien Proposal, 5/31/79
    - Alan Hayakawa on WRC Washington Radio Show on Senator as Washingtonian Magazine's listing of SIH as worst Senator, 1/82 (Box 228)
    - interview with Owen Spann, KGO radio on various subjects, 1/2/92
    - actuality on Disaster Assistance for San Francisco area, 1/11/82
    - actuality on meeting with Japanese officials on trade, 1/12/82
    - interviews: reaction to State of the Union speech; KRON/Audio on withdrawal piece (from campaign?), 1/26/82
    - actuality on Dizier's release, 1/28/82
    - in-House briefing on foreign relations including Poland, El Salvador, Korea, grain, 2/82
    - interview with Sheila Caudle of Gannett on various topics, 2/3/82
    - interview: wrapup on budget with Leo Rennert, McClatchy, 2/10/82
    - interview with reporters on US/PRC enconomic cooperation, 2/25/82
    - Senate Republican Conference Operation Airwaves on Caribbean Basin Initiative, 3/82
    - interview with China Times newspaper on Taiwan, 3/2/82
    - floor statement on Harrison Williams, 3/9/82
    - interview with Rich Indenfuth of ABC on POWs and MIAs, 3/19/82
    - statement on meeting with Japanese Foreign Minister on Japan/US trade, 3/23/82
    - interview with KPIX San Francisco Editorial on various topics, 3/24/82
    - actuality from Operation Uplink on Enterprise Zones, 3/26/82
    - interview with Cable News Network on El Salvador and Taiwan, 3/27/82
    - interview with Dick Hall of McClatchy News on food stanps and guest worker, 3/29/82
    - testimony on Aging Subcommittee (Labor) on Older Americans Employment, 4/1/82
    - comments on meeting on Taiwan arms, 4/12/82
    - interview wth KCET/LA, "Congressional Report"; interview with Don Shannon of LA Times; actuality on trade imbalance between US and Japan, 4/16/82
    - speech to the Washington Junior League at Press Club (biographical), 4/20/82
    - interview with Otto Kreiser on bilingual education, 4/21/82
    - testimony on Bilingual Education Improvement Act; actuality on Bilingual Education Improvement Act, 4/23/82
    - actuality on Administrative Request on PRC laws and congressional consultation, 4/26/82
    - actuality on Disaster Assistance to Anaheim area, 4/28/82
    - actuality on Operation Uplikn on Voting Rights Act Extension and Bilingual Ballotsi, 4/30/82
    - interview with Bill Cooper of KPPC Pasadena, 5/5/82
    - interview on "Take Two" Cable News Network; interview with Hal Cessna on various subjects, 5/18,82
    - testimony an actuality on S.J. Res. 93 on small business contracts, 5/19/82
    - Operation Airways on labor (SIH 4th on tape), 5/82
    - interview with Jeffrey St. John of Washington Times on immigration, 5/24/82
    - actuality on Grape Standards legislation, 6/17/82
    - interview with John Dedmond of States News on various subjects, 6/21/82
    - Operation Uplink of Senate Republic Conference on Work Incentive Act; Operation Airwaves on small business, 6/82
    - statement and actuality on Secretary of State Shultz hearings; statement and questions for Shultz at confirmation hearing, 7/13/82
    - interview with Howard Lesser of Voice of America on Africa trip, 7/20/82
    - interview with Hal Cessna of Cox Broadcasting on Alaska Oil proposal and tax reform, 7/27/82
    - interview with Asian Wall Street Journal on Alaska Oil Proposal and Taiwan, 7/28/82
    - actuality on House Passage of Solomon Amendment (Selective Service and Federal education assistance), 7/29/82
    - interview with Jeffrey St. John on Africa trip, 8/2/82
    - statement and actuality on Support of Balance Budget Amendment, 8/4/82
    - statement and actuality on withholding on dividend and interest income, 8/6/82
    - interview with Cable News Network on PRC/Taiwan Communique, 8/18/82
    - actuality on US troops to Lebanon, 8/20/82
    - Senate Republican Conference Agriculture Forum on Immigration Bill, 9/82
    - actuality on vote to support Reagan on Spending Bill, 9/10/82
    - statement for presentation of Tam of the Month to Rose Varga, 9/13/82
    - statement after Lebanon Massacre news report, 9/20/82
    - Senate Republic Conference Operation Crossroads Africa with delegates, 9/22/82
    - 1981 (Box 229)
  - Videotapes (Box 230)
    - Russian trip with Senator Baker, clips include Belgium/NATO, 1/4-1/11/79
    - press event, National Mime Week with Red Skelton, Washington, D.C., 3/29/79
    - TV program, oil decontrol/Rhodesia/California Politics 1980, Washington, D.C., 5/17/79
    - Public Affairs Broadcast tape produced by Tippi Hedren on Cambodia, Senator Hayakawa on camera approx. 1:00 on Cambodian culture being destroyed plus approx. :20 voice over, "Cambodia, The Final Act?", 8/6/80
    - PSA, tax benefits for the elderly, 1980
    - interview, NBC Today Show: English Language Amendment, Washington, D.C., 4/28/81
    - editorial response: English Language Amendment, Washington, D.C., 7/7/81
    - campaign prepping tape (two tapes): Medfly/Abortion/Small Business/Washington, D.C., 7/11/81
    - taped intro for PBS program on Soviet invasion of Afghanistan, 7/31/81
    - PSA, military academies, San Francisco, CA, 10/5/81
    - PSA, disabled veterans, San Francisco, CA, 10/7/81
    - PSA, Fourth of July, Washington, D.C., 6/21/81
  - Press audio cassettes, 7/81-12/81 (Box 231)
  - Color slides
  - Press audio tapes - Weekly Radio Programs (Box 232)
    - mailbag #1, 6/27/79
    - mailbag #2, 7/10/79
    - mailbag #3, 7/17/79
    - mailbag #4, 7/26/79
    - mailbag #5, 10/24/79
    - mailbag #6, 10/31/79
    - mailbag #7, 11/15/79
    - mailbag #8, 11/29/79
    - mailbag #9, 12/7/79
    - mailbag #10, 12/13/79
    - mailbag #11, 12/18/79
    - mailbag #12, 1/29/80
    - mailbag #13, 2/22/80
    - mailbag #14, 2/28/80
    - mailbag #15, 3/12/80
    - mailbag #16, 3/25/80
    - mailbag #17, 4/30/80
    - mailbag #18 (Senior Citizen interns), 5/16/80
    - mailbag #19 (inflation/10c gas tax/inflation), 5/22/80
    - mailbag #20 (6-day mail delivery/15% interest tax/SBA), 6/5/80
    - Radio Show #21 (Clark/union dues), 6/12/80
    - Radio Show #22 (Social Security payments to convicts), 6/20/80
    - Radio Show #23 (Fourth of July message), 6/25/80
    - Radio Show #24 (Vietnam War Memorial), 7/1/80
    - Radio Show #25 (Women in politics), 7/24/80
    - Radio Show #26 (Our failing welfare system), 7/31/80
    - Radio Show #27 (Iranian dissidents/American Sovereignty Protection Act), 8/7/80
    - Radio Show #28 (Deportation of Iranian dissidents), 8/21/80
    - Radio Show #29, (55 mile speed limit), 8/27/80
    - Radio Show #30 (Arthritis/Dimethyl Sulfoxide/ DMSO), 9/19/80
    - Radio Show #31 (sale of nuclear fuel), 9/25/80
    - Radio Show #32 (First in an eight part series on small business), 10/3/80
    - Radio Show #33 (Second in series on small business), 10/10/80
    - Radio Show #34 (Third in series on small business, increase in SS), 10/16/80
    - Radio Show #35 (Fourth in series on small business: Regulatory Reform), 10/23/80
    - Radio Show #36 (Fifth in series on small business: solar energy), 10/30/80
    - Radio Show #37 (Sixth in series on small business: federal spending/inflation), 11/6/80
    - Radio Show #38 (Seventh in series on small business: reduction in federal paper work), 11/13/80
    - Radio Show #39 (Eighth in series on small business: youth differential), 11/20/80
    - Radio Show #40 (Federal election voting hours), 12/4/80
    - Radio Show #41 (First in series of six on education), 12/11/80
    - Radio Show #42 (Second in series on education: goals of education), 12/18/80
    - Radio Show #43 (Third in series on education: decline in basic learning), 12/25/80
    - Radio Show #44 (Fourth in series on education: television a deterrent to education), 1/1/81
    - Radio Show #45 (Fifth in series on education: busing), 1/8/81
    - Radio Show #46 (Sixth in series on education: government interference), 1/15/81
  - Press tapes - audio (Box 233)
    - Keynote speech, Central Washington University, 5/6/79
    - speech, US Chamber of Commerce luncheon, 5/7/79
    - press conference, JACL, 5/9/79
    - interview with Jimi Ogunlafa, African report, 5/15/79
    - speech, Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, re: Rhodesia, actuality, re: gasoline, 5/17/79
    - commencement address, Pepperdine Law School, 5/19/79
    - speech, San Diego World Affairs Council; interview with Jerry Rankin, Santa Barbara Press, re: Illegal Alien Proposal, 5/31/79
    - interview at White House, re: Rhodesia, 6/79
    - speech, Virginia Bar Association, 6/23/79
    - floor statement, re: food stamps, 6/26/79
    - interview, San Jose, 6/30/79
    - speech, Laguna Niguel Rotary Club; interview, Palos Verdes TV, 7/3/79
    - interview, AM San Francisco; interview with Owen Spann, KGO radio, 7/5/79
    - interview with Hal Cessna, Cox Broadcasting, 7/10/79
    - press conference, California Press (2 tapes), 7/12/79
    - interview with Laura Yule, KIEX TV, re: CETA; interview, KRCR-TV, Redding, 8/8/79
    - speech, town meeting in Santa Cruz, 8/13/79
    - interview, KNTV San Jose, re: oil decontrol, 8/17/79
    - interviews, KPIX and KRON, 8/20/79
    - Q and A, KCBS, 8/31/79
    - speech, San Rafael Rotary Club, 9/20/79
    - interview, National Public Radio, 10/25/79
    - interview with Diane Kiesel, CA public TV, re: draft registration, 12/10/79
    - interview with Rowland Post, KRON TV, 12/31/79
    - press conference, San Francisco, 1/21/80
    - press conference, re: refugees, 1/22/80
    - actuality, re: Canada and US diplomats, 1/30/80
    - press conference, CRA, 2/4/80
    - Reagan Rally, 2/5/80
    - Republican Platform Hearings re: undocumented workers, 2/15/80
    - press conference, Washington, 2/27/80
    - interview: general, 3/80